(Raj:)- Dude, you have totally not moved on.
- Yes, I have.
(Leonard:)It's just a matter
of actually making a date with someone.
- Like who?
- Well, there's Joyce Kim.
(Leonard:)But she defected back to North Korea...
(Leonard:)...so it's a little
geographically undesirable.
- What about Leslie Winkle?
- Oh, no.
- Why?
- Her research methodology is sloppy...
(Sheldon:)...she's unjustifiably arrogant
about loop quantum gravity...
(Sheldon:)...and to make matters worse,
she's often mean to me.
- I think she's smoking hot.
- I'd hit that.
(Sheldon:)You'd hit particulate soil
in a colloidal suspension.
(Sheldon:)Mud.
(Leonard:)Look, I like Leslie,
but she's not interested in dating...
(Leonard:)...as much as using men as tools
for stress release.
Yeah? So? Be a tool.
(Howard:)Go get yourself
a little rebound stress release.
(Raj:)It would only be rebound if he and Penny
had actually engaged in physical intimacy.
(Howard:)You mean like you
and Richard the slave girl?